Preliminary Inventory of the Jef Raskin Papers, 1975-1997
Department of Special Collections
Jef Raskin Papers,
1975-1997
Special Collections M1147
Raskin, Jef
8 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of Jef Raskin, 1999.
Biography
Jef Raskin is an independent consultant on interface design, best known for having created the Macintosh computer project at Apple, the one button mouse and the click-and-drag paradigm for using it, the Apple style of computer documentation, and the Canon Cat and other interface-based products. He was Director of the Third College Computer Center at the University of California at San Diego from 1969 to 1974 and Visiting Scholar at the Artificial Intelligence Laboratory at Stanford University in 1973. In 1974 he formed Anabatic Aircraft, a model airplane company. From 1978 to 1982 he was employed by Apple Computer as Manager of Publications and New Product Review (1978-79), Manager of Applications Software (1979-80) and Manager of Advanced Systems (1980-82). From 1982 to 1989 he was president and CEO of Information Appliance, which created a number of products with innovative interfaces, including SwyftWare for the Apple II, and the Canon Cat for Canon Inc. of Japan. From 1989 to the present he has been an independent consultant and writer.
Series Description
- Email and Correspondence, Series 1.
  - email records, Accumulator 1A [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - email records, Accumulator 1A [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - email records, Accumulator 1B [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - email records, Accumulator 1B [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - email records, Accumulator 2 [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - email records, Accumulator 2 [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - email records, Accumulator 3 [1 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - email records, Accumulator 3 [2 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - email records, Accumulator 3 [3 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - email records, Accumulator 4 [1 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - email records, Accumulator 4 [2 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - email records, Accumulator 4 [3 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - email records, Accumulator 5 [1 of 1] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - email records, Accumulator 6 [1 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - email records, Accumulator 6 [2 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - email records, Accumulator 6 [3 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - email records, Accumulator 7A [1 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - email records, Accumulator 7A [2 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - email records, Accumulator 7A [3 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - email records, Accumulator 7B [1 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - email records, Accumulator 7B [2 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - email records, Accumulator 7B [3 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - email records, Accumulator 8A [1 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - email records, Accumulator 8A [2 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - email records, Accumulator 8A [3 of 3] (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - email records, Accumulator 8B [1 of 3] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - email records, Accumulator 8B [2 of 3] (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - email records, Accumulator 8B [3 of 3] (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - email records, Accumulator 9 [1 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - email records, Accumulator 9 [2 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - email records, Accumulator 9 [3 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - email records, Accumulator 9 [4 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - email records, Accumulator 10 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - email records, Accumulator 11 [1 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - email records, Accumulator 11 [2 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - email records, Accumulator 11 [3 of 4] (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - email records, Accumulator 11 [4 of 4] (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - email records, Accumulator Unanswered (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - email records, Accumulator 12 [1 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - email records, Accumulator 12 [2 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - email records, Accumulator 12 [3 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - email records, Accumulator 13 [1 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - email records, Accumulator 13 [2 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - email records, Accumulator 13 [3 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence [1 of 2]1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence [2 of 2]1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence [1 of 4]1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence [2 of 4]1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence [3 of 4]1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence [4 of 4]1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence [1 of 5]1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence [2 of 5]1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence [3 of 5]1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence [4 of 5]1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence [5 of 5]1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Faxes sent [1 of 2] (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Faxes sent [2 of 2] (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence re: The Humane Interface (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Information Appliance Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence re: Aabius Ten Studies (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to David Wing1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence re: Samuelson-Glusko Survey (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence about planes (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Road Repair (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Banister and Crun (Box 7, Folder 2)
    How to Operate the Inventory Preventive Maintenance and Waste Monitoring Programs, 28pp. (photocopy of manual); Proposals correspondence, app. 150pp.
  - Jorgen Skogh - articles and correspondence (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Electric motor / propeller, 21pp. w/ diagrams; Gottingen Airfoil Polars, 6pp. w/ diagrams; Eistein's Folly, 7pp. w/ diagrams; Practical Aerodynamics for Model Airplanes, 42pp. w/ diagrams
  - Anabalic Aircraft (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to Government (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence re: taxes (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Subject files, Series 2.
  - Commentary on Raskin (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Newsclippings
  - Aerodynamics - Airfoils [1 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Aerodynamics - Airfoils [2 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 9)
    The Actual Velocity Distribution Over an Airfoil, 10pp.; Correspondence, 5pp.; Diagrams
  - Aerodynamics - Airfoils [3 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Aerodynamics - Airfoils [4 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Aerodynamics - Airfoils [5 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Aerodynamics - Airfoils [6 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Aerodynamics - Coanda Effect (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Aerodynamics - Plans (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Drawings; Photos; Diagrams; photos and Brochures
  - Aerodynamics - Planes (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Oshkosh Airfoil Program, 12pp.; Correspondence, notes, diagrams, app. 40pp.
  - Airguns and Bows and Arrows (Box 8, Folder 4)
    The Arrow, March 1997(Newsletter); TL to American Airgunner, 1p.; TL to Airgun News, 1p.
  - Apple Corporate History (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, articles, announcements, memos, copies of agreements, Brochures, newsletters, proposals, app. 35pp.
  - Apple Corporate History - Apple II Documents (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Order information, Labels, Apple Talk(newsletter), February 1981
  - Apple Corporate History - Apple III Documents (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Promotional Poster, Memo, Apple III software proposal, June 12, 1979, 11pp.
  - Apple Corporate History - Articles re: Apple Products (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Photocopies of news articles, app. 20pp.
  - Apple Corporate History - First Macintosh circuitboard (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Apple Corporate History - History of the MacIntosh Project [1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Genesis and History of the Macintosh Project, 5pp., Correspondence, articles, newsletters, app. 50pp.
  - Apple Corporate History - History of the MacIntosh Project [2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Apple Corporate History - Jef's Memos [1 of 3]1977 - 1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Memos, app. 300pp.
  - Apple Corporate History - Jef's Memos [2 of 3]1977 - 1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Apple Corporate History - Jef's Memos [3 of 3]1977 - 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Apple Corporate History - Manuals (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Manuals, correspondence, app. 50pp.
  - Artwork (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Drawings, newsclippings, correspondence, photos, flyers, app. 50pp.
  - Bloxes (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Drawings, newsclippings, correspondence, photos, receipts, app. 50pp.
  - Art Projects - Machine Museum Exhibition MOMA, LACMA (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Newsclippings, flyers, correspondence, press releases, app. 30pp.
  - Box Factory (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Proposals, diagrams, correspondence, app. 50pp.
  - Computer Programs - Flow [1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Flow: A Teaching Language for Computer Programming in the Humanities, Proposals, notes, Offprint, app. 100pp.
  - Computer Programs - Flow [2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Apple Corporate History - MacIntosh Project [1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Memos, schematic drawings, app. 100pp.
  - Apple Corp. History - Macintosh Project [1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Apple Corporate History - MacIntosh Project [2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Apple Corp. History - Macintosh Project [2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Publications, Series 3.
  - Technical Documentation for the Canon Cat Editor [1 of 4], 265pp. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Technical Documentation for the Canon Cat Editor [2 of 4], 265pp. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Technical Documentation for the Canon Cat Editor [3 of 4], 265pp. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Technical Documentation for the Canon Cat Editor [4 of 4], 265pp. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Forth Manual: Documentation for the Programming Language of the Canon Cat [1 of 3], 246pp. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Forth Manual: Documentation for the Programming Language of the Canon Cat [2 of 3], 246pp. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Forth Manual: Documentation for the Programming Language of the Canon Cat [3 of 3], 246pp. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - The Humane Interface, Version 1.0 [1 of 5], unbound (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - The Humane Interface, Version 1.0 [2 of 5], unbound (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - The Humane Interface, Version 1.0 [3 of 5], unbound (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - The Humane Interface, Version 1.0 [4 of 5], unbound (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The Humane Interface, Version 1.0 [5 of 5], unbound (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Humane Interface, Combined notes [1 of 6], app. 500pp. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Humane Interface, Combined notes [2 of 6], app. 500pp. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The Humane Interface, Combined notes [3 of 6], app. 500pp. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Humane Interface, Combined notes [4 of 6], app. 500pp. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Humane Interface, Combined notes [5 of 6], app. 500pp. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - The Humane Interface, Combined notes [6 of 6], app. 500pp. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 2.4 [1 of 4], 405pp. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 2.4 [2 of 4], 405pp. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 2.4 [3 of 4], 405pp. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 2.4 [4 of 4], 405pp. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 5 [1 of 5], 387pp. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 5 [2 of 5], 387pp. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 5 [2 of 5], 387pp. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 5 [3 of 5], 387pp. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 5 [3 of 5], 387pp. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 5 [4 of 5], 387pp. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 5 [5 of 5], 387pp. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 8 [1 of 5], 392pp. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 8 [2 of 5], 392pp. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 8 [3 of 5], 392pp. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 8 [4 of 5], 392pp. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The Humane Interface, Draft 8 [5 of 5], 392pp. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - The Humane Interface, Version 1.0, 427pp. bound (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - The Canon Cat Reference Guide, 152pp. spiral bound (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Canon Cat How-to Guide, 147pp. spiral bound (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Humane Interface, sample design extract, app. 30pp. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - The Humane Interface [1 of 2}, 350pp. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - The Humane Interface [2 of 2}, 350pp. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Essays and Articles, Series 4.
  - Curriculum Vitae (Box 13, Folder 8)
    11pp.
  - Articles and Essays [1 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 9)
    The One-handed keyboard, 4pp. -- Either-or Fallacy, 3pp. -- Pacifia Moods, 10pp. -- The Monty Hall Game, 2pp. -- The J Interface Theory of Operation, 4pp. w/diagrams -- Eliminating the Equals Key on Calculators, 2pp. -- Recollections of a Non-Believer, 2pp. -- Review (of Things That Make Us Smart), 1p. -- Interface Paradox, 2pp. -- Comments on NuevaNet Services Manual, 6pp. -- The Formatting of Diskettes, 3pp. -- Practical RC Design, 2pp. -- Precision: A card game, 3pp. -- Proposal on PEDs, 7pp. -- Measure A, 1p. -- Pseudomodes, 2pp. -- Puckerbrush Suite, 5pp. -- Puzzler, 2p. -- Reb Ross, TV Evangelist, 9pp. -- Quarry problem, 1p. -- Review (of Steve Jobs and the NeXT Big Thing), 4pp. -- Review (of War of the Robots), 4pp. -- Review (of War of the Robots), 6pp. -- Rotation of the Universe, 4pp. -- Saga's of King Arthur's Court, 9pp. -- Shipping Air, 1p. -- Converting the Ace Staggerwing, 5pp. -- Super Easy Email, 4pp. -- Why We Stereotype Human Groups, 2pp. -- Spearpoint, 3pp. -- The Search for Bellingham, 4pp. -- The Princess of Treboth, 3pp. -- The Genesis and History of the MacIntosh Project, 6pp. -- Does the Dive Test Work for Trimming Sailplanes, 1p. -- The Cognitive Psychology of Prejudice, 3pp. -- Applications are the Wrong Idea, 2pp. -- About Anabat and the 1993 Pass, 2pp. -- Unifying Supplynet: A Practical Vision, 2pp. -- Stereotyping, 2pp. -- Unifying Supplynet: A Practical Vision, 2pp. -- Math, Aza, and Ramanujan, 6pp. -- The Swyft and the Cat, 4pp. -- Leap, the Fastest-Known Cursor Moving Method, 5pp. -- Trouble w/ Toggles, 9pp.
  - Articles and Essays [2 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Articles and Essays [3 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Articles and Essays [1 of 2] (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Computers by the Millions, 11pp. -- The Either-or Fallacy, 1p. -- The Dernallians of Manitoba, 5pp. -- Tales of the Aquaphone, 5pp. -- On Abortion, 5pp. -- Guns Again, 3pp. -- Libraries, A Foundation of Democracy, 2pp. -- Library of Aircraft Books, 6pp. -- Down with GUI's, 6pp. -- Dragon Tails, a card game, 11pp. -- One Moving Part: The Dycam All-Digital Camera(review), 1pp. -- Why Johnny and Nancy Should Use the Net Today, 2pp. -- Ersatothenes and the Size of the Earth, 1p. -- We're not Evolving, 3pp. -- Model Airplanes, The Bernoulli Equation, and the Coanda Effect, 10pp. -- Commentaries: Karl Popper, 1p. -- A Century's Changes, 1p -- Labels, 3pp. -- The Annual Frog Raising, 1p. -- Aids and the Tornado, 1p. -- The Number You Have Reached is Too Long, 1p. -- Scutellaster, 1p. -- Seat Belts Don't Save Lives, 1p. -- Future Schlock, 1p. -- Buying the Unheard: Audiophile Suggestions, 3pp. -- What's as Tough and Sensitive as a New-age Detective?(review), 3pp. -- CCRMA Lecture notes, 1p. -- CD-ROM Virginity Lost, 6pp. -- Anita and the Conductor, 2pp. -- The American Dream in Storage, 6pp. -- Scientist Discovers Proof that Aliens Have Invaded the Interface Design Industry, 10pp. -- Canon's Cat Computer (review), 5pp. -- Cars, 2pp. -- Paying for the Unhearable: Audiophile Suggestions, 3pp. -- Homonym-Synonym Step Game, 1p. -- I Make a Splash, 4pp. -- Rationalizing Information Representation, 8pp. -- Character by Character Interaction, 2pp. -- System A, 3pp. -- Sermon, 2pp. -- Why Things Fall Down, 2pp. -- The Greek Alphabet and its Sounds, 1p. -- Widget of the Week, 20A, 8pp. -- Consultant's Analysis - online magazine, 14pp. -- The Raskin-Blum Family Carrom Rules, 2pp. -- The Raskin-Blum Beeper Code List, 2pp. -- Why it Goes so Fast (review), 10pp. -- Learning you're A -B- whats?, 1p. -- Interchange Multipier, 1p. -- A Top-Quality Vacuum Forming Machine (review), 4pp. -- Interface Questions, 3pp. -- Bringing Commercial Advertising to the NET and How to do it Right, 3pp. -- The Lindberg Diesel Tug, 7pp. -- Literals, Names and Numbers, 6pp. -- Magic Trick, 2pp. -- Wring it Out, 3pp. -- Mac and the Mega-Micro Syndrome, 2pp. -- How to Trim Sailplanes for Aerobatics, 4pp. -- Majority ruleth Not, 1p. -- Desidera for Quoting Mechanisms, 4pp. -- Brackets, 5pp. -- Why Mathematics Works to Describe the Physical World, 5pp.
  - Articles and Essays [2 of 2] (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Fish and Richardson (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Documents and Correspondence re: Apple computer vs. Articulate systems, app 50pp.
  - Poetry File (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Poetry by Jef Raskin, 37pp.
  - Forms (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Blank consultant forms
  - Articles (master file) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Listing of published articles and rates
  - My Computer Articles (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Down with GUI's, What's Next for Apple, Looking for a Humane Interface, It's the Interface Stupid, Computers by the Millions, Steve Jobs and the NeXT Big Thing (review)
  - Abel Aabius (Box 14, Folder 8)
    TM, Abel Aabius(1990) - Ten Studies for Recorder Quartet, 73pp.
  - Mac and Me (Box 14, Folder 9)
    TM, Mac and Me, app. 60pp.
  - Mac and Me (Box 14, Folder 10)
    notes, Questions that have been asked, app. 60pp.
  - Machome Journal articles (Box 14, Folder 11)
    It's the Interface, Stupid!; Choosing a joystick
  - Converter Text (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Exploring a Simple Interface, 6pp.
  - Linda's Rolodex (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Addresses and numbers
  - Humane outline [1 of 2] (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Outline and notes, app. 200pp.
  - Humane outline [2 of 2] (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Humane Notes 2 [1 of 2] (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Comments, app. 300pp.
  - Humane Notes 2 [2 of 2] (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Humane Notes 3 [1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Humane Notes 3 [2 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Humane Interface, app. 100pp. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Book for AW ( discarded material)
  - Jef's personal notes (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes, app. 25pp.
  - WE Series (eppler format) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Document, app. 10pp.
  - PC Docs (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Correspondence and notes, app. 50pp.
  - Courses (Box 15, Folder 7)
    A Plane and Easy Approach to Science, 4pp.; Linking Computers to the Curriculum, 9pp.; Outline for a Proposal for an Exhibit, 2pp.
  - Wired Collection (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Correspondence and articles re: Wired Magazine, app. 50pp.
  - Manuals (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Manuals for computer programs and games
  - Aza Raskin (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Images (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Photos of Raskin, planes, etc., 7pp.
- Media, Series 5.
  - Mac Original Missing1997 Sept 5 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Accumulators for Email (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Applications (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Applications (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Encore files within Applications (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Encore Music Applications1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Uncovertible files1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous for Vellum1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Filter Folder1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Jef1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous 21997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - MacHome1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - My Books1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - System Folder1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Preferences1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Vellum1997 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Smog Patterns, 16mm film, app. 20min. (Box 17)
  - Leap Technology by Jef Raskin, 1/2" videotape, 8.35min. (Box 17)
  - Jef Raskin Interview by Peter Jon Schuler, January 1989, casseette tape (Box 17)
  - Jef Raskin Interview by Peter Jon Schuler, march 7, 1997, cassette tape (Box 17)
  - Jef Raskin Interview by Peter Jon Schuler, march 7, 1997, cassette tape (Box 17)
- Calendars, Series 6.
  - Passport1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Business Diary1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Daily Reminder Booklet1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Weekly Pocket Planner,1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Address book (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Weekly Pocket Planner,1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Weekly Pocket Planner,1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Weekly Pocket Planner,1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Diary notes,1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Appointment book,1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)